<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Builds on Tyrian Misfits</title>
    <link>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/builds/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Builds on Tyrian Misfits</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/builds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Basics</title>
      <link>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/builds/basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/builds/basics/</guid>
      <description>The Basics#The core party composition is a support firebrand (primarily for stability), a scrapper (for healing), and a scourge (for condi damage, shields, and boon rips). The remaining two slots are where we can get creative.
At its most simplistic, builds are described in terms of role (DPS vs. support) and position (frontline vs. backline).
Role#In an ideal comp, nobody is a one-trick pony. But it&amp;rsquo;s important to know what your primary role is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elementalist</title>
      <link>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/builds/elementalist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/builds/elementalist/</guid>
      <description>Elementalist#GW2Mists lists two elementalist builds: a support and a DPS.
Support Tempest (Frontline)#Rotation#The tempest is very rotation-focused. There is certainly some tactical thinking required, but less than with other classes. Your job is to rotate through your skills as fast as you can, applying and transmuting as many auras as you can. The precise order will depend on what weapons you&amp;rsquo;re using.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engineer</title>
      <link>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/builds/engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/builds/engineer/</guid>
      <description>Engineer#GW2Mists lists two workable engineer builds: heal scrapper and power scrapper.
Heal Scrapper (Frontline)#Frontline Med-Kit Scrapper
You serve five important functions: stealth, mitigate damage, cleanse, heal, and revive.
Stealth#When commander calls for stealth, use your elite skill Sneak Gyro, which drops a smoke field. Then use your Medkit 5 skill Infusion Bomb, which is a blast finisher.
Pro tip: Double tap Medkit 5 first, then click Sneak Gyro, since Infusion Bomb has a small delay to blast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guardian</title>
      <link>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/builds/guardian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/builds/guardian/</guid>
      <description>Guardian#GW2Mists lists multiple guardian builds. The most common, and the one we need for every single party in the zerg, is the Healbrand. The others can be slotted in to the flex spots, but they cannot replace a proper Healbrand.
Notes on Firebrand Tomes#Anet did what they could to make the tomes quite straightforward to use. The Firebrand page on the GW2 wiki makes it easy to see what they all do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mesmer</title>
      <link>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/builds/mesmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/builds/mesmer/</guid>
      <description>Mesmer#GW2Mists lists a single large-scale mesmer build: the support chronomancer.
Videos#</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Necromancer</title>
      <link>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/builds/necromancer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/builds/necromancer/</guid>
      <description>Necromancer#GW2Mists lists two necromancer builds: a scourge and a reaper. But below are two other builds to consider.
Condi Scourge (Backline)#Kora&amp;rsquo;s Condi Scourge
Your main goal is to spam conditions on the enemies with your AoE attacks with staff and sand shades. Use your wells/serpent siphon along with F5 (Shroud) when tag asks for bombs. Keep your staff marks on walls when we’re sieging. Use scepter 3 (devouring darkness) off cooldown to remove boons from enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revenant</title>
      <link>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/builds/revenant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/builds/revenant/</guid>
      <description>Revenant#GW2Mists only lists a single zerg build for revenant: the power herald.
Power Herald (Backline)#Power Herald
Gear: Use a mixture of Berserker’s and Assassin’s gear. Your goal is to get your crit chance to 60% so you will have a 100% crit rate when you have fury. The trait Rolling Mists doubles the effectiveness of fury, resulting in fury granting you 40% additional crit chance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warrior</title>
      <link>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/builds/warrior/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/builds/warrior/</guid>
      <description>Warrior#GW2Mists lists two large-scale warrior builds.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a good written guide on the support spellbreaker role, including discussions of build variants.
Videos#</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
