<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WvW 101 on Tyrian Misfits</title>
    <link>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/</link>
    <description>Recent content in WvW 101 on Tyrian Misfits</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game Settings</title>
      <link>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/settings/</guid>
      <description>Game Settings#For maximum performance, we encourage you to read the following articles:
 WvW Beginners Settings Guide General Guide For Supporting In WvW Guild Wars 2: Increase/Boost Your Fps and Overall Performance -DirectX 12-Comprehensive Guide 2021  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Etiquette</title>
      <link>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/etiquette/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/etiquette/</guid>
      <description>Etiquette#Running with a squad is like a team sport. To be successful, everyone should understand the fundamentals and adhere to certain basic &amp;ldquo;rules.&amp;rdquo; These basic rules of etiquette apply to any squad you may find yourself in.
  Stay on tag. We cannot stress this enough. If you can&amp;rsquo;t see the tag, you are probably in the wrong place.
  Trust your commander. Even if the lord is at 5%, if the tag says to follow, do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commander Calls</title>
      <link>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/calls/</guid>
      <description>Commander Calls#You may hear the commander call out various words and phrases at certain points. Here&amp;rsquo;s what they mean. Don&amp;rsquo;t ever hesitate to ask, either in the chat or in Discord, if you have any questions or would like to see new terms added.
 blast This is usually called right after stealth. It means to use a blast finisher skill inside of a smoke field to create area stealth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equipment</title>
      <link>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/equip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tyrian-misfits.github.io/docs/wvw/equip/</guid>
      <description>Equipment#Exotic equipment is sufficient for World vs. World. The stat difference between exotic and ascended gear is around 10% – rarely enough to determine a fight. And by playing WvW you will naturally earn Warlord&amp;rsquo;s Armor Boxes, which give you stat-selectable exotic armour. For a discussion of which stats you want on your equipment, please see the Builds article.
If you want to start building an ascended equipment set, start with the trinkets, which are cheaper to get.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
